[wolf howling]
[upbeat rhythmic music playing]
Excuse me. You gotta wake up. Okay?
[groaning]
Come on, wake up.
You should go home. Right?
You… you… you… thief!
[muffled shouting] Help! [grunts]
Look. You wanna be in one piece.
-[groans]
-Right? Shh.
[grunts]
[rock music playing]
[thief groans]
What is this?
Who are you, you crazy bitch?
Hey, just go. Just get lost, all right?
-Go on!
-[both grunting]
Goddamn it! [grunting]
[groaning]
[both grunting]
[groaning] I'm… I'm sorry.
[thief] Please stop!
[chiming]
[both grunting]
♪ Love to hate you ♪
[vocalizing]
[female voice over PA] Passengers
traveling southbound,
please make your transfer
at the next station.
The doors are on your right.
A BRAVE CIVILIAN? OR AN ASSAILANT?
Huh?
[gasps]
[mysterious music playing]
Uh, excuse me.
[man] The culprit suffers from injuries…
Oh my God.
-…that require six weeks of hospital care.
[victim] What do you mean,
violent criminal?
That person saved my life.
-And was it a woman?
-[gasps]
-[victim] It was a man, right?
-[exclaims]
-[line ringing]
-[woman 1] Hey, how was the flight?
You have a death wish, huh?
Just call the cops and let them handle it.
Do you purposely go around town
seeking out men to beat up?
How did you find that out? Even my mom
couldn't tell it was me.
[woman 2] You're just a female thug
and a lawyer on the side!
Hey! What do you mean by "female"?
A thug is a thug.
It's not just men, all right?
Thanks for your concern though.
I'll call you later.
-Hey, hey!
-[line beeps off]
How could you…
answer a call in the middle of this?
Aw, come on, you didn't like that?
Usually, I take calls
in the middle of doing it.
-[groans]
-[grunts]
[playful music playing]
Oh!
What's wrong?
It kinda feels like I'm just some
sort of cheap one-night stand for you.
You know, we could end up dating,
and this could be
our first night of many to come.
I mean, that's possible.
Wow.
We talked for two hours,
and I had no idea.
You're quite the romantic and open-minded.
Most men usually hit it and quit it,
but they'd never consider women
who do too to be their girlfriend.
[moans seductively]
[upbeat music playing]
Womanizer type one.
I'm gonna go rinse off.
Men who really wanted to have
a one-night stand.
-Okay.
-[camera clicking]
[woman 1] For these guys,
they don't care who they do it with.
-Uh…
-I'd like to drink alone.
Come on, you should have stayed home
if that's the case.
-Why would you come here?
-[sighs] Just leave me be.
Oh, come on. I'm being friendly.
Type two. Sex is the only thing
these types of men think about.
-What?
-Don't get me wrong, I enjoy sex too.
But men who're easy, not my cup of tea.
-[dance music playing]
-Womanizer type three.
Hi there. Let's just go with the flow.
There's no need to know names or ages.
-You're married, right?
-[laughs] How'd you know?
-[woman 1] Men who are married…
-Divorced.
[woman 1] …or have girlfriends.
A new addition.
A romantic who likes
the movie Before Sunrise.
[laughs]
I'm surprised he exists.
Shall we get
a couple more drinks and come back?
-I thought you lost the mood.
-[man] Yeah, I did earlier.
But leaving now doesn't feel right.
You like it, then you don't like it.
I'm not really liking your fickleness.
-But you're okay.
-All right. [laughs]
You're pretty chill. I like that.
[both laughing]
Honey.
[ominous music playing]
[sighs]
I don't have to say sorry to you, do I?
We only just met today.
You met him today?
You just met him, and you…
Hon, what's going on? Who is this?
You must have dated her for a while.
I've known Jin-suh for about eight years.
We've been dating,
what, six months?
Seriously?
Whoa, so you're not just chill.
You're coldhearted.
Take care. Bye. Have a good one.
-You son of a bitch! [groans]
-[grunts] Oh, that's--
Don't you ever let me see you again!
Baby. I mean, Ji-yeong.
[sighs]
Too bad we ran into each other
like this, eh? And, man, she seems angry.
"We've been dating for six months"?
Were we really dating,
or were you just sleeping around?
I honestly don't think
you're in a position to complain.
-We're both doing the same thing.
-Same thing?
We end here nice and clean. See ya.
[scoffs]
We're not the same. You were
on your way out, and I just got here.
You've already done it. I didn't do it!
[sighs]
[automated voice] Door closing.
Did you drive here?
It's dangerous for you to drive
while you're mad.
I just want you to drive safely.
Did you already know
that he was two-timing you?
Kinda. Did he ever flip his phone
to hide his screen from you?
Uh… Why didn't you break up with him then?
I don't have to give up
my season pass to Universal
just 'cause I had fun at Disneyland.
It's kind of like that.
And men do this kind of stuff too.
Especially those who are powerful.
[emcee] The Best Actor Award
goes to Nam Kang-ho.
Mr. Nam Kang-ho
already has many nicknames,
"Master of Kiss," "God of Romance,"
and now he can add
"Best Actor in the Country."
Oh, and it's not just in Korea.
He also recently appeared
in a Hollywood film.
This evening, many
of his international fans are here.
[crowd cheering]
[triumphant music playing]
[emcee] Now, please go ahead
with your acceptance speech.
Yes. Well, thank you all very much.
All these years, I'd say
that it's an honor just to be nominated.
But frankly, I wanted
to win this at least once.
[crowd laughs]
I love acting.
It's always been a big part of me.
I couldn't have done it
without, uh, all your support.
I can't single out
each and every one of you. [chuckles]
[crowd laughs]
But I'll try and reach out
to thank them all individually.
And there's somebody
I consider a soulmate,
Do Won-jun, my benefactor
and a good friend to me.
For as long as you will allow me,
I'll be an actor until the day that I die.
Thank you so much!
[crowd cheering]
-[cork pops]
-[upbeat music playing]
[both laughing]
Congrats! You did it!
[sighs]
[upbeat music continues]
[groans]
Hey, you did well.
[sighs]
Congrats to you both for winning
the Best Actor and Best Actress Awards.
-[actress] Thanks.
-Yeah.
[reporter] What would be a role
you'd like to try next?
Cheers.
Maybe a steamy romance
with a handsome young man?
-[chuckles]
[actress laughs]
There are already plenty of men
who do that with younger women.
Am I right? [laughs]
[reporter] Yes. Yes, Ms. Choi Soo-jin.
Why would she say
something like that on live TV, man?
Oh gosh.
[Soo-jin] Right.
[Won-jun sighs]
So it's a crime
when an old man dates a young woman,
and it's a romance
when an old woman dates a young guy?
Hey, did you write this comment here?
[intriguing music playing]
No.
-It's verbatim, word for word.
-No way.
Look at it.
-It sounds like you.
-It wasn't me.
-Well, it sounds exactly like you.
-Let me see.
-Is it my username?
-Here.
Come on. You can always set up
a new account, can't you?
-Okay. So what if it was?
-I knew it.
[scoffs] It's not, seriously.
The comment section is going crazy.
[man 1] In a film, if a woman
beats up a man, it's a comedy.
If a man beats up a woman, it's horror.
[man 2] Women should serve
in the military too.
[woman 1] Bringing up
military service again?
Men should have periods
and get pregnant too.
[overlapping voices chattering]
[man 3] Men: I don't have
enough money to marry you.
Women: you don't have
enough money to marry me.
[woman 2] You can't get married
because you have nothing else.
[man 3] I have plenty of money.
I'm also married.
[woman 2] Sure, funny. I'm busting up.
What should we eat to sober up?
Hey.
Are you okay, sir?
[scoffs] Hey?
[man] What's wrong with her?
Here.
Let's go.
[ominous music playing]
BAD GIRL
[woman] "To the parents
who have raised the attorney Yeo Mi-ran
with great care and love,
you must have spent countless days
praying as you raised
your daughter to become a lawyer."
"The pity you must have felt
as she studied throughout the night."
"How worried you must have been,
lest she get sick during exams."
[sniffles] "There must be
no way you could ever forget
the day when she passed the bar exam."
We'll report this
as a personal info theft.
How did a marriage broker
find out our address?
[tsk-tsks]
[clears throat] "However, the concern
for your child will never end."
"That is because a single marriage
can either make or break a whole life."
"I have 25 years' experience
in the field, and with the heart
of a loving mother, I'm truly dedicated
to helping you find the best suitor for--"
We having breakfast or what?
Why must you read
something like that to the end?
This one is a bit different.
Look, it's handwritten,
not just some printout.
So what? That's supposed
to make her jump with glee?
[door opens]
-Why are you yelling at Mom again?
-Oh, no, he wasn't yelling.
It's just that you've not shown
any interest in any of these arrangements.
Dad was concerned. That's all.
But why does he have to yell at you?
I'm just not interested.
Whoa, whoa, what's this?
How dare you raise your voice at your dad?
So disrespectful.
Come on. Why are you both
at each other over nothing?
I'll make you something.
Eat before work, 'kay?
I have something to tell you.
What's this?
It's the tuition to the law school
you said you didn't want me to go to.
I said I'd pay you back.
Um… [sighs]
ONE HUNDRED MILLION WON
[gasps]
A third of it was from my part-time job,
but I put some more in there for you
for feeding me
and letting me stay at home.
[Dad clears throat]
The reason I was against you
taking the bar exam
was because I was worried
you would waste the money and time
after all that effort. Even graduates
from top law schools fail the bar exam.
[sighs] So I'll be moving.
You're gonna be director then? [laughs]
There's only two of you at the firm.
One's CEO, and the other's director?
No, I mean I'm moving out of here.
I'll be living on my own from now on.
-What is she saying right now?
-Huh?
She said she'll move out.
You disapprove whatever I do anyway.
There's no point telling you.
Mom didn't know either,
so don't you yell at her.
See you later.
Hey, stay for breakfast.
I'm gonna be late.
I'll see you later, okay?
[Mom sighs]
It won't be long
before she's saying goodbye forever.
Why didn't you tell me?
You must have known about this!
I told you not to yell at her!
If you must, just yell at me!
Why must you yell at Mom, huh?
Because she's easy to pick on?
-You rude little--
-Oh, what's the matter with you?
Go to work, okay?
Be careful, sweetie. Get something to eat
when you get to work, all right?
This country is a total mess
because of lawyers like you! Huh?
He took out a loan
worth 40 million in your name.
He spent 20 to buy a car
and saved the rest.
But then, he sold that car
and made another ten.
He made 30 per car loan.
There are 29 cases altogether.
That means there are
29 folks just like you.
But wait, how did he get a 40-mil loan
to buy a car that costs 20?
And with a young guy's name?
There's an insider at the finance firm
who adjusts the credit limit.
That person and the pimp are in cahoots.
[sighs] That son of a bitch.
[tearfully] I really don't know
anything about this.
He told me that he'd pay me
four million a month
if I let him use my name.
After the first payment,
he hasn't received anything for a year.
He really doesn't know
anything, Detective.
[sighs]
Honestly, I didn't know
that guy would do this to me.
[breathing shakily]
And I was so nice to him.
This is so unfair.
Hey. Don't worry.
I won't let you take the fall for this.
-I wanna kill him.
-Of course you do.
They were wrong for that.
I'm gonna catch him and kill him.
You can't actually kill him.
Detective Lee will catch him for sure.
His nickname is "God's Right Hand."
-[crying]
-[baby crying]
[sighs] You met him at a boxing gym.
How could you have let this happen to you?
We met at a boxing gym too.
Should I not be trusting you?
Hey, you, listen.
[continues crying]
[sighs]
Eat some food. All right?
-[continues crying]
-[baby toy squeaking]
Thank you.
I got you.
The food's getting cold, so eat it!
-[gasps]
-[crow caws]
[clears throat]
You know, you're a really good person.
-Hurry up and eat.
-Okay.
[calm, upbeat music playing]
[laughing]
[sighs deeply]
[squealing]
[music slows to a halt]
-[crow cawing]
-[makes sputtering noises]
[Kang-ho] Let's go.
Ugh, this place is so damn far away. Man!
We good?
[Kang-ho] Dude, is it cute
for a grown woman to act like that?
She just lost everything.
She'd be so miserable
she'd want to kill herself. Now she acts
like this 'cause of the nice view?
-Romance writers are all psychos, huh?
-Oh, yeah?
And she's clumsy too.
Why would anyone like her?
Her character's the worst,
but then everybody starts to think
that when she speaks up,
she has conviction.
[squealing]
Well, if you're sick of it,
then just stop watching.
[yelps]
[Won-jun] Let's go.
-Huh?
-The rehearsal.
[sighs]
I'm the one who's miserable, 'kay?
Come on, man.
An action or a film noir role
would be a nice change. I'm sick of this.
Oh, go ahead and do it
if you get an offer.
-Hello.
-Oh, hello. Yes.
[woman 1] Wow, he's so handsome.
Hey, but if you take on those projects,
you'll wind up injured and traumatized.
And you won't get commercials.
-[women] Hello.
-[chuckles] Hello.
-[woman 2] Yes.
-Have you eaten?
-Yeah.
-[woman 3] He's so charming!
Commercials? Ugh!
You're such an opportunist. [scoffs]
Okay. Let's just stay off
romance for a while then.
It'd be nice to rest a bit.
-[woman 4] Hello.
-Hello.
-Oh! [chuckles] Oh, hey, hello.
-[women] Hello.
-We meet again on this project.
-[laughing]
-Let's do this!
-Yeah. [laughs]
[sighs dreamily]
That guy should have been
an actor himself.
He did try once,
but he was really bad at acting.
Ah. So God didn't give him everything.
[Won-jun] Okay,
you're the "Master of Kiss,"
so why don't we show them how it's done?
But it can't just be a kiss.
it has to be sensual.
[inhales sharply, exhales]
[romantic music playing]
Don't close your eyes.
What? Was there a line here?
An ad-lib.
Oh! That was good.
Hey, I think my heart just skipped a beat.
-[chuckles]
-Wow, you've really gotten better.
Not bad, man.
And that thing you just said,
"Don't close your eyes," or something,
ask the director to add
that in no matter what.
Hmm.
And also, don't turn
and bring your face in close like this.
Instead, wrap your arm
around the waist and pull her in.
So if you wrap your arm
around her waist and pull her in,
the girl will be in this position,
so when she tries to pull her head away,
she'll naturally just…
fall back on the couch.
-You see?
-Oh.
Okay.
-Yeah. All right, get in the mood. Here.
-Yeah.
Ready and action.
[breathes deeply]
[romantic music playing]
Don't close your eyes.
[moans]
[groaning]
-Whoa! Ah, shit!
-[laughing]
-Damn.
-That was my bad. [laughing]
-That was on purpose.
-Huh? Bro, I just fell over.
-Oh jeez.
-[laughs] Hey, wait.
That was our first kiss.
-[gasps]
-[Won-jun] What are you saying, nutjob?
-Get off me.
-Oh, wait.
-Damn it, get off!
-Hold on. Okay.
[both grunting]
I'm… I'm sorry.
Hey! Why are you sorry?
Where are you going? Where are you going?
Hey, we're rehearsing here.
Rehearsing the scene!
[sighs deeply]
-Jeez.
-[Won-jun] Why are you shocked?
What's up with the sigh of relief?
[chuckles]
I'm not doing this.
You practice with him from now on.
Come on, why are you so grossed out?
[scoffs]
Well, um…
Oh, yeah, why are you here?
They say the shoot
will be delayed for a bit,
so you should relax and wait here.
Or take a nap or something, yeah?
[Won-jun] What?
That means we won't finish today.
It's Hwang Ji-hye, am I right?
[door closes]
[gasps] What's all this?
Bonus for winning the case.
-Huh?
-I'd say this is better, yeah?
We probably couldn't sell
that empty lot we got last time.
How can this be better?
What will you do with these?
I'll… eat them. You'll eat them.
We'll give them away
and donate them. [sighs]
There wouldn't be a way
to sell all these, right?
Ah! Seung-gu has a truck.
Maybe we can borrow it?
-Oh, really? Good idea.
-[phone vibrating]
[gasps]
Hey, Seung-gu.
We were actually just talking about you.
[Seung-gu] Mi-ran, those assholes
are partying in Jindo.
-I'm going there to catch them.
-What are you doing?
-You there? Huh?
-[line beeping]
What's wrong? He asked for money?
Seung-gu says he's on his way
to catch the pimp.
-Where?
-Jindo.
Where in Jindo?
I wanna kill him.
I'm gonna catch him and kill him.
[gasps]
[gasps] Sung-ho,
call the police right away.
-Do it!
-Oh, sure.
[Sung-ho] I just got a call
from Detective Lee.
They're in Sol Beach Resort.
The room is booked under
the pimp's younger brother.
Did he call the authorities in Jindo?
[Sung-ho] Yeah, he said he did.
-Okay, thank you.
-[phone beeps off]
Oh, Seung-gu.
Seung-gu, please don't cause any trouble.
[sighs]
-[sighs] Please don't cause any trouble.
-I'll be fine.
-[elevator dings]
-[woman] Mr. Do! [panting]
-I… I'm…
-What's up?
-I'm sorry, but I need your help.
-Huh?
She may not listen to the director,
but she may listen to another actor.
What is the issue?
[director] I mean… [scoffs]
You're saying that the reason
you won't put on makeup is you might get
an ad offer from other brands?
As soon as the show comes out,
I'm sure that I'll get an offer.
See, if I were to use
another brand's makeup during the show,
what would the advertiser say?
How about this?
I could just get my hair touched up.
-Do I have to use makeup?
-Okay, okay.
See, there haven't been
any beauty offers just yet.
And I have a scene to shoot.
We've also managed to obtain sponsorship,
so you'll have to work with us on this.
Why must I be responsible
for your sponsorship?
[laughs annoyedly]
It's not my responsibility either.
Do you have any idea how hard things are?
Production is losing money!
Huh? Losing money! In the red!
Can I just confirm?
Did you just raise your voice just then?
[breathing heavily]
I can't just stand here.
I'm the lead. When there's a delay,
I have a responsibility to the production.
The crew are on standby.
We gotta shoot the scene.
I agree, we do.
-But she won't open up to you.
-[scoffs]
[Won-jun] If you go there
and take one look at her face,
you think you can hold your tongue?
The moment you see her face,
you'll lose your temper.
Watching her at the beach scene,
you couldn't stand her.
And there you were,
going on about how awful she was.
I took my meds. I can hold it in.
How many times has
that medicine failed you, huh?
You drove at least ten actresses to tears
even after taking that medicine.
Then I was the only one
who cleaned up the whole mess.
I learned the hard way.
I won't let you get involved
in any situations like this.
Listen.
I won't mess up this time.
For once, just trust me.
No, no. I won't fall for it.
-No way.
-Just once, man.
-No casualties.
-[Won-jun] What do you mean?
-Where are you going?
-[Kang-ho] Thanks.
-Thanks for what?
-[Kang-ho] You're the best.
Hey, you don't wanna do that.
-[Kang-ho] Yeah, thanks.
-Hey!
-[grunts]
-You.
Damn it! Shit.
[both grunting]
Who the hell are you? Asshole.
Damn you!
[grunting]
-Take him inside.
-Get him!
-You're dead!
-Hey! [grunting]
Son of a bitch! Damn it, you asshole.
Get inside!
What? Seung-gu!
Help!
[upbeat rhythmic music playing]
[grunting]
[both grunting]
Hey! [grunts]
[sighs]
[both grunting]
[grunts] What are you doing?
[gangster groans]
[Mi-ran sighs]
[groaning]
-Hey, are you okay?
-Yeah, I'm good.
Ow! [groans]
-Isn't she a lawyer?
-More like Michelle Yeoh.
[all exclaim]
Oh! [sighs] Hmm.
[knocking on door]
[door opens]
Kang-ho. I'm sorry about all this.
It's all right. I'm here to talk to her.
Ji-hye, I'm sure there's
a reason why you're acting this way.
There's something I wanna share
from my years in the industry.
Would you like to hear me out?
As you can see,
we are really lucky to work here.
The director's nice, and there're
no last-minute script changes.
This script was finalized a week ago.
So, let's just go with this one.
The crew are all waiting on us.
Okay?
[whines]
This is how it is.
We just make do and shoot.
What do you think?
Huh?
[whines softly]
But, Kang-ho, this is different.
This is a scene
where the director said
I'm supposed to be getting pretty
so I can go on a date with a guy.
So I came up with an idea.
Instead of putting on makeup,
I was thinking maybe
something like this would help.
[squeaks]
Like this.
[whines softly]
Or this. [inhales sharply]
And… [giggles]
Or a cute smile like this? [giggles]
[Kang-ho] Cheap flirting
shows that you have no class.
Or maybe… sexy could work.
[provocative music playing]
Maybe like…
[chiming]
Just like that.
I'll pretend to tie back my hair
and show him the nape of my neck.
[Kang-ho] Again, it's cheap, not sexy.
Please stop.
[grunts]
[door opens]
[crows cawing]
Ji-hye! Huh?
What are you doing? Hurry.
-Ji-hye! Just talk to me.
-Hey, stop!
Ji-hye, stop running!
-My legs are hurting!
-Oh no, she's leaving!
-[director] Ji-hye!
-Hurry!
Ji-hye! Oh, seriously? Ji-hye!
-You're really annoying me right now.
-[engine starts]
Ji-hye, please open up, 'kay?
Open the door.
Oh my gosh, stop! Oh, come on.
What do we do now?
She can't just leave like this!
-What do we do?
-[crying]
-Ah, what do we do?
-Why does this happen to me?
[groans] She's really-- Oh jeez!
-But still there's a chance.
-I don't know. Call her!
Oh! Oh, wait!
[sighs]
Bro, I didn't say anything. I swear.
I just said that the crew was waiting
and we should just go with the script.
-[grunts]
-[exclaims]
[intriguing music playing]
And somehow she stormed out
looking that angry?
Well, of course she was acting ridiculous,
so she might have seen it on my face.
But I wasn't being mean to her
or anything, dude!
The security camera.
Don't they have them inside?
You can check to see if I said anything.
[groans]
If I had known this would happen,
I would have just said
what I was thinking.
Hey, are you an actress?
-Are you in this just for commercials?
-[groans]
You won't get any commercial contracts.
You know why?
'Cause you really suck!
[grunts]
At the boxing gym,
you were taking it easy.
-You studied physical education?
-[Mi-ran] No, silly.
I did humanities. I went to a law school.
Ah, that's right. You're a lawyer.
[both laugh]
-Where's your car?
-Uh, over there.
Oh, yeah? Mine's here.
I guess we'll part here.
Just get home safely, okay?
You really helped me out. Thank you.
Okay. Just remember to work hard
and be good to your mom.
[chuckles]
-See ya.
-Okay. See ya later.
-[laughs]
-Bye.
[sighs, humming]
She's just trying to find herself
a mega-rich guy,
so why does she even work?
So she can bring up her status.
Because she thinks
that if she raises her value,
everyone will bid on her, right?
[ominous music playing]
After all, that's
every woman's dream, I suppose.
[scoffs]
-[Won-jun] Are you finished?
-[Kang-ho] Yeah.
-[Won-jun] Then get in the car.
-You aren't coming?
[Won-jun] The director is
a mess right now. How can I leave?
-I didn't do it. Hwang Ji-hye did it.
-Just get in.
[ominous music continues]
[sighs]
-[van door closes]
-[engine starts]
[Kang-ho] Because she thinks
that if she raises her value,
everyone will bid on her, right?
NAM KANG-HO, THE GOOD ANGEL
NAM KANG-HO, MAN OF MANNERS
After all…
ATTENTIVE, HAND MANNERS
…that's every woman's dream, I suppose.
LEG MANNERS THIS TIME
[Mi-ran] It's a new type.
The vampire.
Here's your beer.
It's kind of a psychopath type, you know?
They win the hearts of women,
then they live off that energy
yet think women are worthless
and only see them as prey.
[gasps] No way. And it was him for sure?
Yes, I checked to make sure.
Nam Kang-ho and Hwang Ji-hye
had a shoot right there.
-Then was he just rehearsing?
-[sighs]
Hey, who gets all angry
while rehearsing a script?
Also, even if it was out of context,
there's no way he didn't mean it.
He's basically a misogynist
who treats women like something to be won!
[groans]
I was such a big fan of him.
No, it can't be true.
You must be mistaken.
[sighs] How much do you know about men?
You always go for the handsome ones.
Do you have any idea how men talk
about women when they're alone at night?
Love? I don't think so.
Women are just for sex,
and they're objects for ownership.
When their girlfriends dump them,
they watch porn!
Porn! They use it to comfort each other.
No joke!
And they also feel superior
as if they can toy with women's hearts.
They're just a bunch
of assholes by nature.
They cower before those who are strong
and trample on the weak.
And all they want to do is
to categorize women as the weaker sex.
-[sighs] It's hot in here.
-Not all men are like that, you know.
Oh, there's one. An exception.
I know, why'd you dump him?
He's a rare breed.
And he's actually kinda cute too.
Did I date him?
What do you mean, I dumped him?
Oh gosh. Hey, Na-eun, it's been a while.
How have you been?
-[Sung-ho] Excuse me. I'd like one too.
-[server] Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
Wow, the subordinate gets off work early
and is drinking,
and the boss stays and finishes work.
What a dream job you have.
[laughs] Oh, come on.
Mi-ran has to work so much
because money's so tight.
Hey, do you know
who wants to buy potatoes or useless land?
What do you mean?
Don't say it.
We got paid
with potatoes and an empty lot.
Huh? They didn't pay you the fees?
[Mi-ran sighs] It's not like that.
Sung-ho made the deal
right from the beginning.
-Oh, here!
-[server] Here's your beer.
Mi-ran and Na-eun,
congrats on your freedom, huh?
I wish you good luck!
Yeah, thank you very… munch.
-[Mi-ran, Na-eun laugh]
-[Sung-ho laughs awkwardly]
Where are you?
You still with the director?
Yeah. Don't worry about me, okay?
Sorry, bro.
Good night.
-[Kang-ho] Okay.
-Yeah.
[phone beeps off]
[sighs]
[drunkenly] Look, Kang-ho is
really, really worried about you.
He's worried sick.
You know what he said earlier?
Kang-ho wants to cheer you up.
-Aw, Kang-ho is so great!
-[Won-jun laughing]
[laughing] Oh, thank you so much.
I know you must be very busy, Mr. Do.
Oh, you see, I'm just…
-I'm just doing my job, you know.
-[sighs]
It's been so long since we've been able
to share drinks together.
-And it just makes me really happy.
-[both laughing]
-I mean it!
-Oh yeah, by the way…
It was Hwang Ji-hye who caused
all that trouble. She hasn't called once.
Because of her, I'm so upset. [crying]
Oh, wow. This must be so hard for you.
I'm sure Ji-hye
is also feeling very sorry right now.
Don't worry about it.
You know, I will talk with her soon,
and… I'll make sure the show goes on!
-[gasps] Thank you.
-Mm-hmm.
I'm really counting on you, Mr. Do.
Leave it to me. [grunts]
-[baby toy squeaks]
-Whoa, whoa, hey. Wait, wait, wait!
What do you think you're doing?
You're already so drunk.
Why? Let's go somewhere
and have another drink!
[sighs]
-Goodbye! Have a good night.
-[Won-jun] Okay, get home safely.
Okay, have a good night.
-[moaning]
-[grunting]
Oh, thanks a lot!
-Hey, are you okay?
-Oh, yeah. I'm good.
Just hang in there.
Your cab is almost here.
Mr. Do, you know, I'm…
I'm really stressed.
I get pushed and tossed around,
and I'm so stressed.
[sighs]
Okay.
I know, I know. You're in the middle,
getting pushed around,
and you do have the toughest job.
I know that, really.
[laughing] That's why
we should have another drink.
Just one more.
-One more drink!
-Oh, wow. Look.
-Oh, look at the time. It's late.
-Oh, come on, please!
One more drink.
There's a place right here. If I buy--
-[retches]
-Huh? Whoa, whoa, whoa. W… wait. Hey.
I'm fine.
-You good?
-Yep. [gulps]
You swallowed it?
-Yes, yes.
-Here, come on, look here!
-Look at me straight!
-[moans]
Listen to me. I think
that you should head back now.
-'Kay.
-Or you will regret it.
You know, when things are really hard,
you might not wanna do anything
that'll make it
more difficult for yourself.
-Isn't that right?
-Mm-hmm.
[car horn honks]
Here.
Yeah, the cab, the cab.
Here, here, here. Get in.
This will take me home?
Oh, of course. This will take you
right to your home. Mm-hmm.
I'll see you tomorrow!
When tomorrow comes,
you're gonna thank me for sure.
You know,
one of the worst things
a human being can go through
is the pain of embarrassment.
-One-point-five billion?
-[cash register rings]
Hey, why would you tell him that?
Her security deposit
is also all from a loan.
So that's why, you know?
Doing good deeds is good, but please do
other work that will bring money too.
[sighs] She's the head of our household.
She says she'll cover 70%.
Oh, what are you worried about?
We make enough money to get by, right?
Mmm, no, that's not it.
Would it be okay if I lived with you two?
It would just make everything easier.
Oh! Good idea.
We have three rooms, so we could do that.
Well, I guess so.
I…
[intriguing music playing]
…am really good at cleaning.
And I'm great at cooking too.
Is that so?
[heart beating]
Hmm, look at this.
You still have feelings for me, right?
So how's this gonna go?
Well, feelings are just feelings.
I won't do anything to you.
It'd be nice. Just think about it.
I'm notifying my landlord.
Hmm.
[footsteps approaching]
A picture is worth a thousand words.
I'm glad I didn't tell you I was coming.
[intriguing music continues]
Mmm, uh, Eun-jung.
Uh, what are you doing here?
What brought me here
was the high-speed train,
then I followed you.
Just because we're a weekend couple,
I can't see you on the weekday?
We've been dating for seven years.
We're basically married.
Sung-ho, is this true?
Eun-jung, hey, let's go outside and talk--
No, I don't want to! I followed you here.
I'm pathetic, not ashamed.
Who are you?
Me?
Eun-jung, hey!
I'm a lawyer who works with him,
and this is my friend.
[sighs]
-You told me you work with a man.
-[gasps]
-What are you to Sung-ho?
-Uh, there's nothing between us.
There's nothing between you,
and you hold his hand like that?
Are all women in Seoul like this?
-You girls are so loose.
-Um, what'd you say?
-Eun-jung!
-Excuse me. You better watch your tone.
-Don't insult my friend like that.
-Why can't I insult her?
-She's the one my man cheated on me with.
-No, I'm not!
Eun-jung, what are you doing?
You're embarrassing me!
-Come outside!
-What are you doing? I should be upset!
Wait a minute.
Be honest with me.
Is she telling the truth?
You've been together for that long?
-Ooh, that's, uh…
-[wolf howling]
[gasping]
Uh, excuse me,
but the truth is your boyfriend
is the one who has wronged you.
Even if he's cheated on you,
it's sickening that you're blaming her
and taking it out on her
instead of your boyfriend.
Hey, that's enough, okay?
Eun-jung, I'm sorry, okay?
We shouldn't do this here. Let's go.
-This is all part of being in love.
-Ah, let go!
-Why are you dragging me out?
-[Sung-ho] Come on!
-[sighs]
-[Sung-ho] Come out!
-[grunts] Let go of me!
-You shouldn't be like this.
-Just say that you don't wanna be with me.
-[sighs]
Why did you lie?
What? You work with a man?
-Busy on weekends?
-I've been busy!
We were just having a drink
for the first time in a while.
And the hand-holding earlier?
It's a misunderstanding.
All right? You've misunderstood.
What are you saying?
Then why didn't you tell her about us?
[scoffs]
And "I love you, heart, heart,"
who was that?
Come on, Eun-jung!
-Did you look at my messages?
-[exhales sharply]
Do you know
how many times I drank with him,
to comfort him after a breakup?
[laughs incredulously]
How did I not catch on for three years?
Even you couldn't know everything.
Even monkeys can fall from trees.
Well, okay. What I didn't know
is what I didn't know.
But this asshole had the guts
to get me to introduce my friend to him?
You can't. [laughs nervously]
You can't beat him up, okay?
-[sighs]
-You'll still work, right?
-What?
-With Sung-ho, I mean. [laughs nervously]
You'll keep working, right?
Are you asking if we're still gonna be
colleagues even after this went down?
[sighs]
[sighs] I'm sorry.
I didn't know he was that kind of guy.
But you see?
Men simply cannot be trusted at all.
Even one who is a… [scoffs] …good one.
Even if it's my friend,
you can never trust men.
No exceptions. [sighs]
But do lawyers
get paid unemployment?
Ah! Oh, don't worry about the money.
I'm a lawyer. Cha-ching!
-You think I can't make money?
-[laughs nervously]
You're right.
[Mi-ran] I was never this affected
even when I dated a jerk.
I lost my only male friend today.
The last hope I had on men…
vanished just like that.
CLAIM FOR DAMAGE
[Jin-suh] If you withdraw from the show,
you'll be liable
to pay for the current production costs
at 7.9 billion won
and any additional costs of the reshoot.
If Mr. Nam Kang-ho
wouldn't agree to a reshoot,
you'll have to pay separately
for any resulting damage.
-[sighs] She's not dropping out!
-[thunder rumbles]
-A shoot can be delayed…
-[moans]
…due to an actress's health reasons.
If a shoot is delayed
without a doctor's note,
you may be sued for damages.
Right now, I simply can't see
Mr. Nam Kang-ho face-to-face
because of the mental shock
I had suffered.
I heard that from my friends,
but Nam Kang-ho is totally two-faced.
On camera, he acts like he's nice,
but he's really cruel when he's not.
If what you just said gets released,
it'd be spreading false information,
and it's grounds for a defamation lawsuit.
It's not false information.
I swear I heard it.
Do you think the public will believe you?
They gave him the titles
of "The Angel of Good Deeds,"
"Mr. Heartwarming."
Will they believe
this ten-year top star actor,
or do you think
they'd believe Hwang Ji-hye,
who's only done two projects
and is amassing anti-fans?
[splutters] What?
As of today,
your anti-fan base has reached…
[exhales deeply] …27,368 members.
[lawyer] Oh, that's
three more than yesterday.
Therefore, we hereby inform you
that the burden of pausing production
vests solely on Ms. Hwang Ji-hye
and that Mr. Nam Kang-ho
is completely unrelated
to the matter at issue.
-Yeah.
-Yep.
Go back to the shoot.
It's all because you were being difficult.
[Ji-hye] You're the one
who got my hopes up, Mr. Yoon.
You told me I would get a good deal!
How dare you talk to me like this!
-Come on.
-You're making me look bad!
-You told me to do that.
-Take her out of here!
GILMU
LAW CORPORATION
[mimics mechanical whir]
[sighs] Mr. Do is amazing, huh?
He prepared evidence
for a situation like this.
-Gilmu!
-I know, right?
[Soo-jin] If you keep this up,
I'll find a new law firm!
[grunts]
Hi! You're here.
Ms. Choi is rather… agitated.
-[sighs]
-Hmm?
I only said that if she leaves her home
without a valid reason, it'd be
disadvantageous for her divorce.
That's why I'm asking you to make it
so I don't have to deal with that!
[sighs]
How could you assign me
a young boy who's not even been married?
Get me another lawyer.
Mr. Ko, how about you personally
take care of Ms. Choi on your own?
[chuckles] Of course.
I'll be looking into your case,
but shouldn't there be
another designated lawyer?
Oh, no. I can't communicate with a man.
Get me a female lawyer.
But, madam, there's no female lawyer here.
If you don't get me one, I'll have to tell
Mr. Do to take our business elsewhere.
Ah, come on. You've gotta be kidding me.
We don't have one just yet.
We just have to hire one.
[sighs] However, I'm not sure,
would that new hire
even live up to your standards? Hmm?
Call me when you have interviews.
I wanna sit in.
-I'm leaving.
-Oh, madam.
Take care and have a nice da--
[groans]
[amusing music playing]
Oh gosh, she drives me crazy!
[groans] Damn it!
-What are you gonna do?
-Of course we'll have to hire one.
She's a huge client.
She brings in billions to us. [sighs]
A woman.
She'll be a headache.
They take menstruation leave
and maternity leave.
They complain about discrimination
and inequality.
Imagine if they had to join the army too.
-Ah!
-[chiming]
Could there be one who's ex-military?
[Mom over phone] Wow, look at the view!
Oh, wow, that's so amazing.
[laughs, gasps]
It… it's beautiful, huh?
Will she live on the window?
Everyone's saying, "The view, the view!"
-That's enough. For crying out loud.
-[Mom] It's really amazing in person.
Here. This is the living room.
And over there, do you see the kitchen?
Oh, it's really huge.
Wow, and this is… Na-eun's room.
Do you see her?
-Na-eun, say hi.
-Hello, Mr. Yeo.
[Mom laughs]
Ah, now I'll show you Mi-ran's room, 'kay?
-[humming]
-[calm music playing]
Huh?
Are you going out?
Uh, to work.
-Right now?
-[sighs] I have a lot to do.
I'll see you when I'm back.
[Dad] Hang up.
Hey.
Come on, say hi.
[grunting]
I said hi to him earlier.
Hurry up and tell him,
"Come over after we unpack." Here.
[clears throat]
Come over after we unpack.
It's fine. I've seen it all.
Why do you talk to her like that?
Mmm.
You should be proud that she's earning
enough to live on her own, okay?
[sighs]
Oh, Mom, please go home.
Come back when we're unpacked.
-What's there to unpack?
-[glass clatters]
[gasps] Hey, mister, mister!
You can't put that there.
-Not there!
-[sighs]
[Mom] Be careful with it.
I'll show you where things go.
And these over there and in there.
Hey, take it easy.
I'll do it when I get back here.
-[laughs] Good luck.
-[Mom] This in that room.
[grunts, laughs]
CHOI & YOON LAW FIRM
[interviewer 1] We'll be in touch.
[chuckles]
[sighs, clicks tongue]
WOOSUN LAW
[interviewer 2] We'll be in touch.
[sighs deeply]
[solemn music playing]
YS LAW OFFICE
[interviewer 3] Thank you
for your interest. We'll be in touch.
[interviewer 4] I'm so sorry,
but we'll reach out to you next time.
[interviewer 5] See you some other time.
[interviewer 6] We can't accept you
at this time.
[interviewer 7] We'll be in touch.
[interviewer 8] I'm sorry,
but we'll reach out to you next time.
[sighs]
Hey, Ms. Lawyer.
What are you doing here?
[sighs]
What do I do?
I guess I'm not as good as I thought.
I'm just a fraud then, huh?
Things didn't go well?
Mmm. Probably not.
There are plenty of law firms out there,
and I'm sure you'll get a call eventually.
[sighs, whimpers]
But there's not many left now.
Civil rights lawyer sounds nice,
but I only got into it
because there wasn't anywhere to go.
I wanted to save face,
and I ran out of options.
Who cares about losing face
in front of your dad?
I mean, sure,
you worked hard to become a lawyer
because you wanted to prove
to your dad that he's wrong.
You've been doing pretty well.
Don't beat yourself up about it.
Oh, damn it. I should have stopped you,
not followed you.
How are we gonna pay for all this now?
[sighs] Oh, don't worry about the rent.
I'll make it. It'll be okay.
I won't let you suffer,
and I know that it's hard.
There's nothing to suffer.
There'll be fewer flights next month.
They're accepting early retirement.
[groans]
[phone vibrating, chiming]
-Someone text you?
-Mmm.
Whoa. Even a pro
gets rejected by text now?
Ah, shit. I'm an experienced lawyer,
not a rookie.
[sighs] What?
GILMU LAW CORPORATION, CONGRATULATIONS
ON PASSING THE APPLICATION REVIEW
-Huh?
-What is it?
What? A job?
Oh! This firm may still hire you!
Jin-suh works there.
-The bully firm.
-Oh.
-But what do I say?
-[car horn honking]
-Why is a woman here?
-She won't get it.
[footsteps approaching]
[sighs]
-[man] Are you Ms. Yeo Mi-ran?
-Yeah, thanks.
[male applicant sighs]
[footsteps approaching]
[intriguing music playing]
[cat meows]
[chiming]
Why did she stare at me like that?
She's the celebrity here.
-[elevator dings]
-[upbeat rock music playing]
Hello.
Hello. How have you been?
[women giggling]
Oh, hello.
-Oh my God.
-Have you been well?
Oh, yes. [spluttering] Yes, Mr. Do.
-I'm sorry?
-Do you remember me?
Oh, of course I do.
Ji… yeon.
[laughing]
-[Won-jun] Am I right?
-[Ji-yeon] Yes!
Oh, he'll treat everyone to lunch today.
-[gasps]
-Really?
Let's all go eat together.
-Ah, yes. Thank you.
-[women] Thank you.
-Yep.
-Ah, yes.
-[woman] I can't even think straight.
-[women chattering, giggling]
You seriously remember her?
Oh, what was her last name?
-[moans]
-[women exclaim]
-Are you okay?
-I'm fine.
Uh, I don't know.
Jeon Ji-yeon?
-That wasn't it.
-Hello.
-[male applicants exclaim]
-Yes. Hello.
-Hi.
-[Mi-ran] He's a client at this law firm?
She's just trying to find herself
a mega-rich guy,
so why does she even work?
So she can bring up her status.
Because she thinks
that if she raises her value,
everyone will bid on her, right?
[ominous music playing]
After all,
well, that's every woman's dream,
I suppose.
[Mi-ran] If he hadn't smiled like that,
I might not have done it.
[energetic pop music playing]
[groaning in slow-motion]
[exhales deeply]
[energetic pop music continues]
[upbeat pop music playing]