LOVE TO HATE YOU
EPISODE 2
BAD BOY
GILMU'S ATTORNEY
GILMU'S MANAGING PARTNER
I can see it now
This is the last love for me
Please don't hurt me anymore
I hate to see…
PRINCESS: JOHNNY'S AUTOGRAPH!
1,818 WON SENT
SIGNATORY YEO MI-RAN
You can hate me instead
So get rid of any lingering affection
Don't you ever look for me again
Because I'll end up hurting you
Take it away from me
Squishy
Did you say my lips are like jelly?
What do I do?
What if you come quietly to me
And beg me for a kiss?
What do I do?
How are you so good at guessing
What I want and wish for?
Just like a magician
Casting magic spells
You grab me and shake me
I don't know, you can tell me
A thousand times, I still wouldn't know
I want to know how love feels
It's driving me mad
Noisy…
Take care of me…
Because you made me this way
I am the best
Open my closet, put on the freshest outfit
Have a good look at my face
I see in the mirror
It's 8:00 p.m. now
And I'm supposed to meet up at 8:30 p.m.
Walk into the night with sassy steps
I'm the best
Subtitle translation by: Daham Yoon