I'm sorry.
It was wrong of me.
PRESIDENT DO WON-JUN
And then?
Yeah?
If you whimsically apologize,
and I whimsically forgive you, that's it?
The director and the crew?
What about them?
Ah…
I'll say sorry to the others too.
Ah. How will you do that?
Mr. Yoon, what am I supposed to say?
You'd better bow down
to each and every crew member
the same way you just did now.
What?
If you don't do as I say,
I'll make sure you're done for.
BAD BOY
Did you see that look?
"If you don't do as I say,
I will end you."
-That's what it said.
-I know!
Now, do you see
what I've been telling you?
It was even worse then.
He treats the female lead this way?
"Mr. Romance?"
-I've had enough of it!
-That's what I'm saying.
That's why I did it.
You said, "Do as you please."
You did well.
Hey, she caused that mess herself.
She deserves this and more.
-So how did you do it?
-Do what?
I reached out to Gilmu.
And they said the production company
would probably take legal action.
Nice.
Ugh, you little…
What, what, what? What's wrong?
I'm embarrassed just thinking about
what the Gilmu guys would say about this.
You only ever pick fights
with women, seriously.
"Mr. Romance" Nam Kang-ho turns out
to be insufferably nasty and petty.
That's probably what they'll think.
And it's not like you've met
any of the lawyers over there.
They're probably gossiping like crazy.
I'm not even sure
if we can keep this a secret.
How about I… take them out to lunch today?
What?
Gilmu Law Corporation.
Let me explain what they're like.
There she is!
There! There she is!
Hey! Hey, wait! Okay. Okay, please…
GILMU'S ATTORNEY
Were you
aware of the plagiarism?
Tell us how you're feeling.
We're innocent.
Our songwriter worked hard on it
for six years.
And we've been listening to it for a…
They specialize in entertainment
and represent celebrities.
GILMU'S REPRESENTATIVE
They have a clearly defined view on life.
"Kill two birds with one stone."
Party with the celebrities
and make money too.
Either they endure the shame,
or they just don't have any.
-Welcome.
-I'm here for the interview today.
-Ah, yes. Right this way.
-I appreciate it.
-Of course. Take care.
-You're welcome.
The biggest problem
is that this is an all-male law firm.
They do not hire female lawyers.
-Why is a woman here?
-She can't get the job.
-Are you Ms. Yeo Mi-ran?
-Yeah.
I know
they called me back as a formality.
And I'm here despite knowing that.
I'm that desperate right now.
The odds may be terrible,
but I can't help taking the chance.
Why are they all men?
I only saw one woman out there.
Uh, yeah, I know.
Uh, maybe they think we only hire men.
You should've said
female candidates only.
No. No way. We couldn't post that.
Oh jeez.
Uh, what was her last name?
I don't know.
Was it Jang Ji-yeon?
That wasn't it.
Hello.
He's a client at this law firm?
Because she thinks
that if she raises her value,
everyone will bid on her, right?
After all,
that's every woman's dream, I suppose.
If he hadn't smiled like that,
I might not have done it.
I mean, I did want to do it,
but it was purely on impulse.
Well, what's done is done.
A good poker face is
a basic requirement for a perfect crime.
Aw.
What now?
Laugh.
-Bro, come on.
-Laugh.
-What?
-Just laugh.
Here, I got you.
There you go!
Well, I hope you enjoyed my show.
Damn, that was embarrassing.
Why did I overdo it
with all that laughing?
It was painfully obvious I was trying
to cover up your humiliation. Ah, damn!
Know what?
They tried to take me out.
Uh…
Okay. Let's just forget about it.
It's plausible enough.
Catch a man off guard, and of course
he's gonna laugh awkwardly about it.
-Dude!
-Huh?
They tripped me, I'm serious.
Wait, hold on. The security cameras.
Check the footage.
Then what, huh?
They get to see you fall again,
and you get to see them laugh at you?
You want to do comedy now?
Cool, cool, yeah.
It's over. Let's just move on, okay?
Okay. Yeah.
But who would have done that?
Hello.
I'm sure you know
Ms. Choi Soo-jin, the acclaimed actress.
She is our VIP client,
so she will be conducting
your interview with me.
-I see.
-Please sit down.
So, tell us about why
you want to join our firm.
Why even bother asking that?
She's here for the money.
Yes. Absolutely.
What was your previous area of practice?
I've worked in many areas,
both civil and criminal.
Have you done divorce proceedings?
Huh?
Oh, yes. Absolutely.
How'd it go?
Winning and losing
are not so clearly defined in divorces,
but they were all partial victories.
-So I can say I've never been beaten.
-Mmm.
-Mm-hmm.
-Are you married?
-Uh, no.
-A boyfriend, then?
We actually just recently broke up. Uh…
They don't ask things like that
at job interviews these days.
Do you have a lot of experience dating?
Would it be bad if I said I have a lot?
Not at all.
It's better if you have a lot of those.
It means you're
well-suited to what we need.
Oh, absolutely.
I have a ton of dating experience.
To what extent? How many have you had?
I haven't kept count,
but excluding casual dates,
15 people?
Are you a player?
It's more like data collection
on different types of men
that are out there.
Oh!
Let's hear about your, uh, aspirations.
What kind of mindset
will you have once you're here?
Everyone says they will do
their best if they're hired, right?
Why don't you show us
some of your special talents?
Sorry?
That way I can see…
just how important this is to you.
I've done talent shows before,
but they've never gone super well.
Oh my.
Show of strength is a no-go.
If you'd rather not, we can move on.
No, please. I have something.
It's called… "You'll cringe so much
that you'll want to kill me."
I do feel like killing her.
Ah!
-Kill her!
-Kill…
Uh, wait, are you streaming this?
Huh?
Thank you.
-Sure. Of course.
-Me too.
-Oh my gosh!
-No problem. Yeah, of course.
One, two, three.
His success rate is 100%, right?
-With me, one with me.
-For what?
-Sleeping with any woman he wants to.
-No way it's 100%.
Well, you're not at 10%,
so how could you imagine 100?
-Hey.
-One, two, three.
I got dumped
because I got caught cheating, okay?
We even got into the hotel
but then got caught
right in the hallway, man.
Okay. One, two, three.
-Why was your girlfriend at the hotel?
-It's not…
Oh my gosh.
Hey, it's not what you think.
I want a picture too!
So I heard you made a move on Lia
and got shot down bad.
No one knows,
but… it was the opposite.
Hey, are you kidding me?
Why on earth would Lia…
Wait, seriously?
Take a picture of us.
-May I hold on to you?
-Oh, sure, sure.
Thank you!
One, two, three.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
-Oh, thank you.
-Yes. Thank you.
-Thank you so much.
-Of course.
Oh, I ordered sushi for everyone,
if that's okay with you.
-Oh, yes. We love it.
-Great. Enjoy your lunch.
-Okay, goodbye.
-Take care.
-Thank you. You too.
-Bye.
He's such a sweet guy, isn't he?
You know, good-looking guys
are often nice too.
It's the average ones
that act up, isn't it?
You're right, you're right.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
Oh my goodness.
Thank you so much.
When the employees get to meet
a big star like Mr. Nam Kang-ho,
they feel… proud to work here.
I bet.
Ah, you ladies hit the jackpot today,
didn't you?
They aren't listening.
Oh, by the way, the chairwoman…
I mean, Ms. Choi Soo-jin is here.
-Really?
-Ah. Mr. Do.
-What brings you here?
-What are you doing here?
Oh… Uh…
Remember how I said I didn't think
my lawyer understood me very well?
Well, President Yang here says
he's going to hire me a new one.
A female one.
You're making it seem
like I forced you to.
That's true.
Hmm.
Did I take it too far?
Hello.
Do you work here?
Uh, no. I actually just came
for an interview.
Ah.
I thought you seemed okay earlier.
I was trying to play it cool…
because I was embarrassed.
In fact, it hurts so much
that I may have to go see a doctor
in case there's a fracture
or a muscle tear.
-You wouldn't be walking with a fracture.
-Oh, yeah?
Try doing this.
Can you do this?
Uh, ow.
Anyway, I don't think it's fractured.
A light contusion, at worst.
By the way, um,
you didn't record it, did you?
-What?
-Me falling down earlier.
No.
Jeez.
What kind of person do you think I am?
Look.
Hmm.
Well, I hope that you feel better soon.
Going down.
She didn't record it,
but I know it was her.
If you wanted
a different lawyer, you should've told me.
Why would you… why would you come
all the way down here personally?
-You have to be careful about that.
-Well, I have Gil-mu's full support.
You're upset I came without you?
I wouldn't say upset. I just…
You can't just do things
without a discussion, okay?
Is that so?
No one tells me what to do,
but I'll always listen to you.
You know that.
Hey, Kang-ho.
Hi, Kang-ho.
We hardly ever see each other,
even though we're repped
by the same agency.
Hello.
Anyone interested in going for tea?
I have the rest of my day open.
-Let's go.
-Huh? Right now?
Mmm?
-Cheers.
-Cheers!
Ah!
Ah, you know what?
Spontaneous drinking is the best kind.
-I'll have another.
-You chugged that whole thing?
All right, well, have mine.
I didn't touch it.
Okay. Are you sure?
-I'm driving.
-Ah, right.
By the way, why do you suddenly want
a female attorney?
Oh…
The guys are always so busy
kissing up to me, they barely do any work.
You know women are busy flirting
and slack off on work too.
-What?
-Mmm.
So, then, I guess you don't even want
pretty girls flirting with you?
The pretty ones are the worst.
They think they can do whatever they want.
That's why you don't have a girlfriend.
Or, um, you haven't been dating at all.
Maybe you're… gay?
You can talk to me if you need to.
I like people like you.
They understand other genders so well,
and they usually have a lot of talent.
Oh, women always love gay guys.
Isn't it every woman's dream
to have a gay best friend, or am I wrong?
Sorry to disappoint you.
You don't have to be sorry.
It's not like I'm trying to become friends
with you or anything like that.
Oh, by the way,
when am I throwing the party for my award?
-Let's find a date soon.
-Tomorrow, you think? Tomorrow's good.
-What?
-Tomorrow? That's pretty short notice.
They don't call me
"Ms. Unpredictable" for nothing.
Anyway, I'm sure
that those who want to come
will find a way to come, as always.
Come on. Who would dare
turn down an invite from you?
There's one.
The one who makes an excuse
not to come out. Hmph.
He's in the same agency as me
and hasn't even shared a meal with me.
Kang Ho-dong once said that what makes
you a family is sharing a meal together.
Oh, right. Should I invite
the folks at the law firm too?
Isn't it about time
we did a company dinner?
For sure. That's a really good idea.
Wait. You know what?
I think that we should have
the two of you as cohosts.
Our staff are all busy,
and it'd be a hassle to host
two separate parties.
-It's perfect.
-Maybe some other time.
-Let her have hers first.
-Well, I don't like it either.
Our tastes are totally different.
I doubt you even know how to party.
Everyone approaches parties differently.
For me, my enjoyment isn't
the most important thing.
Right. But if I'm good,
to hell with everyone else, though, right?
Okay, that's enough.
That's good. Enough. Yeah?
The both of you can party as individuals.
And as soon as one
of your contracts expires,
please, you should find
a different agency to join.
I don't care which one it is.
You can both leave if you want to.
-Eh…
-Ooh…
-Won-jun, hey!
-Dude.
Oh, come on, we weren't fighting.
You know we both
tend to be direct when we talk.
We'll cohost, okay?
We're in the same agency, aren't we?
Oh, yeah, I could do that.
Mmm?
Bravo!
Mmm.
Can't I just show up right at the end?
To pay the bill?
If you don't knock it off with all that,
I'm gonna get really angry.
PRINCESS: JOHNNY'S AUTOGRAPH!
I thought Johnny was too busy to go?
He'll be there for sure. He's a good kid,
and he shows up anywhere you invite him.
Why? Did the little princess
request his autograph?
How'd you know?
You only make that face
when the little princess
send you a message.
Seriously, could you please try to be
as nice to other women as you are to her?
Even half as nice would be huge!
If you did that,
I wouldn't have to work so hard!
Don't you dare touch your savings.
I told you I'd pay the rent.
I won't.
I relieve stress
by putting money into my savings.
1,818 WON SENT
And please don't cause
any more trouble, okay?
We can't afford to be sued.
Relax, I'm just doing this to save money
on a gym membership, I swear.
Any word on a job yet?
Is it possible
this feeling of being nagged
stems from my own insecurities?
-Do you have any more interviews or not?
-Still waiting to hear from two places.
Where are you going?
-Convenience store.
-Convenience store?
Do you know how much more expensive
that is than a supermarket?
Relax. I'm not buying anything.
It's for a part-time job.
Yes, hello?
Seriously? Okay, I understand.
I appreciate it.
I totally got it.
-Which one?
-Gilmu.
Oh.
Why? It's Lee Jin-suh, I'm guessing?
Be excited. You said yes, right?
Of course. Why wouldn't I?
-But why did they pick me?
-Oh, come on.
You're an incredible lawyer!
You win cases, you're healthy,
and you're personable.
I've never seen another lawyer
so perfect in every way.
Ah, congratulations.
But you were just yelling.
Was I? When?
Ah! So, what are we eating?
We'll go shopping.
Do you want meat or sushi?
-Meat!
-And red ginseng?
I went up against all
of those guys and beat them all.
The one place that reached out
and grabbed my hand in my darkest hour.
As the first female attorney at Gilmu,
I'm going to do my best.
Let's go!
In order to enter into a contract with us,
you must first sign this agreement here.
Okay.
I will not mention to others
anything regarding the private affairs
of my clients.
If I violate the above terms,
not only will I be held liable
for civil suits,
but I will also pay
triple my annual salary…
Triple, triple!
…as payment for my penalties.
Are we in agreement?
Oh.
Yeah.
SIGNATORY YEO MI-RAN
Well, you've signed the contract,
so you're one of us now.
Which means we can talk more freely, no?
-Yes.
-Okay.
The confidentiality agreement
is effective as of this moment,
so keep that in mind.
-Yes, sir.
-Okay.
The virtues you must possess
at this law firm are,
primarily, quick wits and understanding.
Our main clientele are celebrities,
and they are a very temperamental bunch.
Their ups and downs can be severe.
They don't even read the contents
of petition drafts. They're above that.
Just try to maintain
a friendly relationship,
take their side, give them your support,
and they'll completely trust you.
If they feel you're neglecting them,
though, the complaints begin.
Ah.
The worst of all is the lady
from your interview, Choi Soo-jin.
I see.
And from now on,
she'll be assigned to you.
Just do whatever she says,
whether it's related to the case or not.
Give her what she wants,
and everything will be fine.
-Yes, sir!
-Any questions?
Sir?
Questions for me?
Oh… You're President Ko Yong-woo,
aren't you?
That's right.
I'm sorry, but I thought Yang Gil-mu
was the president of this firm.
Wait, do you know someone here?
I just heard it somewhere.
Well, now that you're in our gang,
you should know who the leader is.
The man from the interview, yeah? That was
CEO Yang Gil-mu that you met with.
Ah!
On paper, he's the paralegal manager.
Ah.
-A non-lawyer ownership.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa. Something wrong?
Uh, no, sir.
Oh, are you done?
Uh, attention please, everyone!
Yeah, yeah.
I am pleased to announce that as of today,
our firm finally has a female attorney.
Uh, why don't you introduce yourself.
Hello, I'm Yeo Mi-ran.
I'm excited to…
…work with you all.
So, I would like to ask
for everyone's full support
to ensure that Ms. Yeo here
gets settled in as quickly as possible.
-Yes, sir.
-I'll give you a rundown. Over there…
How old is she?
-She's my ex-girlfriend.
-Lying through your teeth still, huh?
She was the one who left.
The hotel?
Okay. Would someone
please take Ms. Yeo for a company tour?
-Oh, Mr. Seo--
-Sir. Allow me.
-Okay, Mr. Lee.
-All right.
Oh, one more thing.
We have an all-hands dinner today
with Dowon Entertainment, okay?
I already drank yesterday too.
Oh, you can drink again.
Don't make a fuss about it.
Things weren't going well at my old firm.
So I decided to leave,
which wasn't easy at all.
I know it could be awkward for you,
but don't worry. I won't cause trouble.
Things must really be bad.
You never really cared for our firm.
Hang on. I actually said that?
You didn't have to.
I could tell. I couldn't tell
you were cheating on me, though.
And this is the nap room.
There isn't a women's one.
That's okay.
Uh, you know,
because I don't plan to sleep here.
This is the company gym.
Unfortunately, there's
no shower for women.
Oh.
If you wanna wash up…
…I'll be your security.
Okay, you got it.
The cafeteria.
Drinks and snacks are all free,
and you can bring in
all the booze you want.
Ooh. How nice.
-Have a seat.
-Sure.
Aren't you busy?
I'm a salaried lawyer. I'm never busy.
We don't care if the trial
gets delayed or goes on forever.
Thanks so much.
Did you sleep together that night?
Jin-suh.
Look, I apologize for suddenly popping up
in your life again,
but let's just try to stay coworkers here.
Mr. Lee, help me out.
-Help you out, huh?
-Yes. Please.
-You're a real jerk, you know that?
-I know that.
That's why
I keep asking you like this.
No problem.
-I'm a chill guy, after all.
-Yeah, you are.
Oh, this must be
like a classic Hollywood friendship, huh?
Oh, we'll see.
Take care.
What… friendship?
Huh.
I'm sorry.
I apologize for my past actions.
-I apologize for my past actions.
-What's she doing?
Is she actually being nice?
Don't close your eyes.
Cut! Okay.
That was great.
-Any problems?
-No problems.
He's a beast on camera
and a gentleman when it stops.
Damn, my heart is pounding.
That kiss scene was so amazing.
So you're all good with Kang-ho, right?
Some friend he is.
That wasn't a kiss
he learned from a book though.
Kang-ho doesn't have
any scandals that we know about.
Oh my.
Damn it.
Oh, damn.
Not even my meds work for her.
He must have an upset stomach.
-He's gay.
-What?
Do you know what would happen
if this got out?
Maybe that's how he's avoided scandals.
That would make sense, huh?
Oh.
This way!
-Hurry, hurry. Yeah, yeah.
-Seat belts! Come on!
-Get in!
-Everyone's in. We're good.
Everyone's in. We're good.
Ms. Yeo. Drink.
-Drink it all. Drink, drink, drink.
-Whoo!
Ah!
Wow, that perks you right up.
I haven't been able to upgrade
my repertoire. What should I do?
Oh, don't worry about your repertoire.
Listen, just back them up
when they're doing their thing.
And always remember
to cheer them on, all right?
-Yeah!
-Yes, sir!
You know, our clients
really do bear their all to us lawyers.
Imagine how vulnerable they feel.
Especially as celebrities, you know?
Always afraid of some kind of scandal.
Just think, how degrading would it be
if they were the only ones feeling naked
and us lawyers were always composed.
Absolutely!
That's why we embarrass ourselves
every once in a while.
-That's right.
-It builds a tight bond of camaraderie.
-Talk to 'em!
-Is that thoughtful of us, or what?
Ah, yes.
But I'm a little concerned.
Uh… you think it will be
a tad too much for this lady?
To be honest,
I'm not really that ladylike at all.
Ooh!
Ah! In that case, we're upping the ante!
Ah! Let's go,
let's go, let's go, let's go!
Come on, let's go. Whoo!
-Dance with me, sir.
-All right, all right!
-Yeah, yeah, let's go!
-Oh, yeah, yeah, here we go now.
-Hey, look at her, look at her.
-Oh, you've got moves.
You guys can't hold
a candle to me in anything.
Yeah, you know it!
Let's go!
Do I really have to win?
Yeah!
Right! So I was like…
I'm glad I fired you!
-Yeah!
-Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Hey!
Wait. Hey, have you met
Mr. Do Won-jun yet?
She's the first female attorney
Gilmu's ever hired.
Now Ms. Choi Soo-jin's her client.
That's right. I'm Yeo Mi-ran.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
It's a pleasure meeting you too.
-Look, I know you'll take good care of…
-Mmm.
…our dear Ms. Soo-jin.
Of course. I'll do my best.
Yes?
-I'm going to the men's room.
-Oh, yes!
Hey!
And that's for you!
-I saw your pink undies!
-Hey, what are you doing?
Talk to my agent. He'll get you a pair
of my pants. There's some in the van.
Great job!
Go, go, go!
Don't turn around. Just go.
Great! That's good.
All right, everyone.
Are we having a good time?
Yeah!
Just so you know, we are lawyers.
All right, let's keep that energy going,
because next up
is our newcomer initiation!
Why don't we all give her a hand?
Do what you did yesterday.
-So good!
-Go, Ms. Yeo! Go, Ms. Yeo! Go…
I really did want to strangle her.
You know
the whole routine, don't you?
Of course you do.
You're a brilliant actress.
Yeah!
You can do it!
-You can do it!
-Oh!
-Yeah!
-Preemptive dominance.
I have to take charge
before they think I'm weak.
What are you doing?
-Calming yourself down because I was late?
-No.
What a relief.
As long as it wasn't me, right?
Someone in there
has seen you fall down, man.
That time you fell down
like a complete idiot.
So, then why are you out here?
I'm embarrassed.
I'm the one who fell down,
so why do you care?
Seriously, why did I overdo it
with the laughing?
Ah.
It was pretty awkward.
I'd be super embarrassed too.
Good for you, though.
Quitting acting was the right choice.
-Shut up and get inside.
-Yeah.
One of the worst things
a human being can go through
is the pain of embarrassment.
What are you gonna do?
What are you going to do?
Ooh!
-Don't panic.
-Whoo! You can do it!
Don't panic. Don't panic.
If I panic now,
I'll never live it down.
Thank you. Thank you.
That was fantastic. Wow.
Mr. Nam Kang-ho, how are you?
What in the world
is this bizarre specimen?
Damn it.
I shouldn't have tripped him.
Here. Here, sit here.
You're good.
-Oh, hey.
-Oh, hello.
-Yeah.
-It's been a while.
Go, girl!
I totally get
the absurd camaraderie
men can have in their work lives.
I'm just disgusted by it.
Wow, she really loves to sing, man.
I wonder why it never gets any better.
-Yo, yo, yo. That's her?
Yeah. You remember her, right?
Oh, yeah. Absolutely.
Very good! Yeah!
-Johnny!
-Johnny?
You have a singer's name,
so get up here and sing!
Come on up, Johnny!
-Johnny.
-You can do it!
Let's have a drink.
Yeah, yeah, Johnny, Johnny. Hey, look.
Kang-ho really wants your autograph, man.
He's been talking about it for days.
Get it before you forget.
And maybe do it outside.
Inside's a bit nuts.
-Be sure to write something good.
-Yes, sir. I understand.
He has a shoot on Jeju in the morning.
Send him straight home
when you get outside.
Okay.
Yeo Mi-ran!
Yeo Mi-ran! Yeo Mi-ran!
Yeah, see?
Did I pick the right person,
or what?
All right, everyone raise your glass.
Okay, cheers!
-Cheers!
No!
Are you drunk?
Come on.
I'll see you later, Mr. Nam.
Yeah, you take care.
-Have a good one.
-Sure thing!
Baby, you are so cool.
-Be quiet!
-Huh? Huh?
There's no one here but us.
Mmm.
Oh, take it easy.
Sexually harassing a coworker.
What?
However, I'll let it slide
under one condition.
You and I are
strictly coworkers from now on, okay?
Huh, what?
Go wash your face.
-Ooh!
-Ah!
It's dirty here. Get up. Hey, get up.
Ah, jeez.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey. Wake up.
-Wash your face.
-I won't wash my face, damn it.
I'm not washing my face.
Uh, what are you doing?
Uh…
-You just see if I wash my face.
-Hey, Mr. Lee.
Are you upset
because of your torn pants, huh? Huh?
That's why you shouldn't have lost
at rock, paper, scissors. Oh!
Jeez.
Ah, well,
so you embarrassed yourself
in front of your ex.
But you really livened up the mood.
I laughed so hard I split a seam.
Guess your pants…
…did too.
Did you even open
your fly before you peed?
Yeah.
Ugh, this guy.
Hey. By the way,
did things really end between you?
You…
What?
You look terrible.
Here, here, here. Where do you live?
I'll give you a ride.
Let's go!
I live pretty far.
Go home and rest, okay?
Hey, Yeo Mi-ran, I'm the one
who got this job for you.
I asked them to give me a female lawyer,
and that's why they hired you.
So do you think you should be
a good girl to me or not?
I was hired because I'm a woman?
So, now tell me where you stay.
-I need to go to the restroom.
-Oh, the restroom? The rest…
-You should go. Hurry up.
-Okay.
Whoa, whoa. Are you okay?
Not in the slightest.
But you know that.
I act like I'm having fun,
but I'm really not.
Aw, what's wrong, darling?
Huh? So you had a good time for a change.
-Mmm.
-Come on. Let's go, let's go.
-I can drive you home myself tonight.
-You will?
You really want to do that?
Do you feel like taking my car or yours?
Whichever one's closer.
I was so happy
that I had bested all those guys.
So this is what
reverse discrimination feels like.
Oh!
I'm sorry.
No need to apologize.
You weren't… waiting for me, were you?
What?
Oh, no. Why would I wait for you?
Well, it would definitely make
a lot of sense.
You know, because of
your… performance before.
Oh, look, that was just--
I think you have a knack
for getting men's attention, don't you?
-Huh?
-You even landed my attention.
It was you at the office, wasn't it?
I felt when your foot touched mine.
You must have felt
when my foot touched yours, no?
This man is a VIP client.
What do I do? Deny it to the bitter end?
If you deny it
to the bitter end…
Okay, I'm sorry.
The truth is, I stretched out my leg
at the wrong time that day.
I'm really sorry.
Lying to me won't help you out here.
But because you recognize
that I'm not a fool,
that means you aren't one either.
So, since you mentioned it…
did you really stretch at the wrong time?
-It wasn't intentional?
-What?
There are women who do anything it takes
to make sure you don't ever forget them.
It's true.
I see their faces, ask their names,
take pictures, and sign autographs.
And really, to be honest,
there are so many
that I can't remember every one.
But the ones who decide to hurt me
without a care in the world,
those are the ones
that I just cannot let go.
They really are pathetic.
Oh, I'm not like that. I was stretching
my leg, and it just happened to--
If that was the case,
you should have said you were sorry.
I'm attacking an innocent person?
Is that the point
you're really trying to make?
I would've dropped it
if you just apologized,
but if you really did nothing wrong,
then prove it.
Let's go check Gilmu's security footage.
That way we'll know once and for all
if it really was an accident.
Um, wait.
I'm really sorry.
I did it, okay?
Because I'm such a huge fan of yours!
It's just… I really like you.
I… I just wanted
to touch you once, that's all.
I'm so sorry.
Come on.
Here's a tip,
be more careful with your love.
You hear me? Okay?
Yes.
I will, I promise.
I'm not the first person
to throw away their dignity
just to put food on the table.
I've never confessed
my love to a man before,
so whatever happens… happens.
Where did everyone go?
I just know her type.
She pretends to be easygoing
and gets men to drop their guard.
Then she seduces and uses them.
-She says she's a fan of mine.
-Hmm?
But I think it'd be best
if she stays away from me.
Mmm.
Different woman, same problems, huh?
-Yeah.
-What about Ji-woo?
-You get along fine with her.
-I don't know anymore.
I can't stand these girls.
Hmm?
Dude, isn't that Ji-woo?
-Ji-woo.
-Hi.
-What are you doing out here?
-I was just, um… waiting for you.
It's been a while.
You look great.
Yo, you forgot this.
Are you hungry?
Why are you dressed so light?
Come here, let me give you a hug.
You must be freezing.
Let's go inside.
Okay.
See you around. Good night.
Have I been cursed somehow?
I can't stand these girls.
Yes!
Uh-oh. Oh!
Yes! At least they're outside now.
What's this?
Here. Have a good night.
Guys really are the worst.
POLICE
Seriously? Is he actually
the president in disguise?